Where? I'd love hay.
hay: n. 干草
premiered on ABC.
premiered: （戏剧、电影等）首次公演（premiere的过去式和过去分词）
The show, in which a young, bachelor horse
bachelor: n. 学士；单身汉；（尚未交配的）小雄兽
is forced to reevaluate his priorities
reevaluate: vt. 再评估；重新估计
as broad and saccharine and not good,
saccharine: adj. 含糖的；极甜的；和颜悦色的
but the family comedy struck a chord with America
chord: n. 弦；和弦；香水的基调
I parked in a handicapped spot. I hope that's okay.
handicapped: adj. 残废的；有生理缺陷的
Is that the proper nomenclature?
nomenclature: n. 命名法；术语
life is just one long, hard kick in the urethra,
urethra: n. [解剖] 尿道
from a long day of getting kicked in the urethra,
you just want to watch a show about good, likable people
likable: adj. 可爱的
Did I already say the thing about the urethra?
urethra: n. [解剖] 尿道
What have you been doing since the show's cancellation
cancellation: n. 取消；删除
18 years ago?
Morning, sunshine.
sunshine: n. 阳光；愉快；晴天；快活
Why so gloomy, roomie?
gloomy: adj. 黑暗的；沮丧的；阴郁的
roomie: n. 住在同室的人，室友
First of all, we're not roommates. You are my houseguest.
roommates: n. 室友（roommate的复数形式）
houseguest: n. 在家过夜或暂住的来客
I've had tapeworms that were less parasitic.
tapeworms: n. 条虫；绦虫类（tapeworm的复数）
parasitic: adj. 寄生的（等于parasitical）
you secretly have a good heart.
secretly: adv. 秘密地；背地里
that you meant you were lazy.
lazy: adj. 懒惰的；懒洋洋的；怠惰的；慢吞吞的
Did you say you've had tapeworms?
tapeworms: n. 条虫；绦虫类（tapeworm的复数）
That's unfortunate.
unfortunate: adj. 不幸的；令人遗憾的；不成功的
Just an issue with the bank and a lack of money in it.
an: art. 一（在元音音素前）
to publish your memoirs,
memoirs: n. 回忆录
Look, we really need a bestseller here at Penguin.
bestseller: n. 畅销书；畅销书作者；畅销商品（等于best seller）
Aren't you an editor at a major publishing house?
an: art. 一（在元音音素前）
but it turned out it was a takeout menu.
takeout: n. 外卖；（桥牌中）示意搭档改叫的叫牌
We're kind of counting on your autobiography
autobiography: n. 自传；自传文学
Have you considered working with a ghostwriter?
ghostwriter: n. 捉刀人；撰文者；受雇代作文章的人
You're wearing that to the prom?
prom: n. 毕业舞会（为中学生举办的正式舞会或聚会，通常在高中学年即将结束时举行）
I improvised that line.
improvised: adj. 即兴的；临时准备的
Because "nay" means no,
nay: adv. 不；甚至；不仅如此
*Three little orphans one, two, three*
orphans: n. 孤儿（orphan的复数）
You're just bummed out because Princess Carolyn
bummed: adj. 不高兴的；烦恼的.
Hey, check out the rug on that guy.
rug: n. 小地毯；毛皮地毯；男子假发
Stop embarrassing me.
embarrassing: adj. 使人尴尬的；令人为难的
You have my undivided attention.
undivided: adj. 专心的；专一的；未分开的；完整的
cruller?
cruller: n. 油炸小煎饼
I'm kidding, jeez. It was Emily Mortimer.
jeez: int. 呀
I never explicitly said that.
explicitly: adv. 明确地；明白地
What? What? What? No, no, wha...
wha: abbr. 世界卫生大会（World Health Assembly ）
Oh, jeez, here we go.
jeez: int. 呀
What is this, a crossover episode?
crossover: n. 交叉；天桥；转线路；变向运球过人
You're being sarcastic,
sarcastic: adj. 挖苦的；尖刻的，辛辣的
So would it be awkward if I joined you right now?
awkward: adj. 尴尬的；笨拙的；棘手的；不合适的
Yes, actually, it's very awkward.
Yeah, this is awkward right now?
awkward: adj. 尴尬的；笨拙的；棘手的；不合适的
It's called being polite, BoJack.
polite: adj. 有礼貌的，客气的；文雅的；上流的；优雅的
Always a Clydesdale, never a Clyde, eh, BoJack?
eh: int. 啊，嗯！（表示惊奇、疑问等）
where the premeal bread isn't free.
premeal:
You've seen me naked. Do you think I'm getting chubby?
chubby: adj. 圆胖的，丰满的
Couldn't hear you over the sound of my calories not metabolizing.
calories: n. [物] 卡路里（热量单位，calorie的复数）
metabolizing: vt. 使新陈代谢；使变形
So yeah, technically I was dumped,
technically: adv. 技术上；专门地；学术上；工艺上
eating cotton candy until I barf
barf: vt. 呕吐
You never took me home, jerk!
jerk: n. 肌肉抽搐；性情古怪的人；蠢人；急拉
Okay, jeez.
jeez: int. 呀
What about as my ex-girlfriend?
ex: prep. 不包括，除外
You look like a pile of crap ate a second pile of crap
crap: n. 废话；废物；屎；拉屎
and then crapped out a third pile of crap.
crapped: n. 废话；废物；屎；拉屎
crap: n. 废话；废物；屎；拉屎
Wait, wait, so which pile of crap do I look like?
I'm not calling you as your ex.
ex: prep. 不包括，除外
Well, Penguin wants an update on your progress.
an: art. 一（在元音音素前）
masturbating to old pictures of yourself?
masturbating: （对……）进行手淫（ masturbate的现在分词 ）
I was masturbating to what the picture represented.
This company is in dire straits.
dire: adj. 可怕的；悲惨的；极端的
straits: n. [海洋] 海峡；困难（strait的复数）
I know kindergarten is scary,
kindergarten: n. 幼儿园；幼稚园
We're hiring you a ghostwriter.
ghostwriter: n. 捉刀人；撰文者；受雇代作文章的人
from the Swamp Monsters swag box.
swag: n. 赃物，掠夺品；摇晃；大量
Because you have an amazing story to tell.
an: art. 一（在元音音素前）
Easy for you to say, you hippie.
hippie: n. 嬉皮士；嬉皮模样的年青人
And that's for trying to sell E on the cartel's turf.
turf: n. 草皮；泥炭；跑马场
She went back to Mexico City, ese,
ese: abbr. 电气支援设备（lectrical Support Equipment）；东南东（East South East）
We had sex last night, dummy.
dummy: adj. 虚拟的；假的
This lady probably thinks I'm just some dumb sitcom actor.
sitcom: abbr. 情景喜剧（situation comedy）
impossible-to-pronounce last name.
pronounce: vt. 发音；宣判；断言
Why are you so obsessed
obsessed: adj. 着迷的；无法摆脱的
I can't even afford a hall now for my daughter's 15th birthday,
th: abbr. 真实航向（True Heading）
You owe me a party, cabrón, and if you don't deliver...
cabr:
Everyone thinks that I'm just this washed-up hack,
hack: n. 砍，劈；出租马车
Toast. I smell burning toast!
toast: n. 干杯；烤面包；接受敬酒的人；（在某领域）广受赞誉的人
Oh, my God, my toast!
That's right, sweetheart.
sweetheart: n. 爱人；心上人
We might have gone too dark on that series finale.
finale: n. 结局；终曲；最后一场；最后乐章；尾声
I don't want to know what spicy feels like.
spicy: adj. 辛辣的；香的，多香料的；下流的
It was a salsa joke, people.
salsa: n. 洋葱做的辣调味汁；萨尔萨舞曲
You've been overstressed.
overstressed: vt. 过分强调；过分拉紧（或紧张）
Will you just call the ghostwriter already?
ghostwriter: n. 捉刀人；撰文者；受雇代作文章的人
Really, not even a pity laugh?
pity: n. 怜悯，同情；遗憾
You can invite the ghostwriter
ghostwriter: n. 捉刀人；撰文者；受雇代作文章的人
Senor Horseman, I will never forget your generosity today.
generosity: n. 慷慨，大方；宽宏大量
Is this a quinceanera?
quinceanera: n. 成人礼
is a quinceanera?
Now who's racist?
racist: n. 种族主义者
I find that pinata offensive.
pinata: n. 皮纳塔，彩饰陶罐
I have a Virgin of Guadalupe pendant to present.
pendant: n. 下垂物，垂饰
Is this a crossover episode?
crossover: n. 交叉；天桥；转线路；变向运球过人
I'm furious.
furious: adj. 激烈的；狂怒的；热烈兴奋的；喧闹的
Oh, I'm... I'm sorry, I don't want to mispronounce your name.
mispronounce: vi. 发错音
Sorry I haven't really been mingling.
mingling: v. 混合；交际；联合（mingle的ing形式）
I get kind of awkward at parties.
awkward: adj. 尴尬的；笨拙的；棘手的；不合适的
I'm probably just overthinking it
overthinking:
You're at a party, compliment the host.
compliment: n. 恭维；称赞；问候；致意；道贺
most of your adult life on some dumb sitcom,
sitcom: abbr. 情景喜剧（situation comedy）
Who wants an autograph?
an: art. 一（在元音音素前）
autograph: n. 亲笔，手稿；亲笔签名
how miserable he should be. I envy that.
miserable: adj. 悲惨的；痛苦的；卑鄙的
envy: n. 嫉妒，妒忌；羡慕
That is profoundly sad.
profoundly: adv. 深刻地；深深地；极度地
- Good Lord, that's depressing. - No, it's not.
depressing: adj. 压抑的；使人沮丧的
Well, finishing my memoir, I guess.
memoir: n. 回忆录；研究报告；自传；实录
You're only my ghostwriter starting nah...
ghostwriter: n. 捉刀人；撰文者；受雇代作文章的人
nah: adj. 没有；很少， 很小
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait a second.
whoa: int. 惊叹声；咳！
This penis has been inside this vagina.
penis: n. 阳物；[解剖] 阴茎
vagina: n. [解剖] 阴道；叶鞘；鞘